Sharvari A. Sangle

Cell: 612-735-2279 E-mail: sangl003@umn.edu
Portfolio: http://sangl003.github.io/Portfolio/

Summary: 3 years of experience working as a GIS analyst in different environments and development platforms. Seeking a full-time position in a fast-paced, customer focused and challenging company to put to good use, and enhance my GIS skills.

Education Year Grade

Master of Geographic Information Science Fall 2016 GPA:3.72/4.0

University of Minnesota, Minneapolis

Bachelors of Engineering in Information Technology June 2011 GPA:3.7/4.0

University of Pune, India

Work Experience:

Minnesota Department of Transportation - GIS Mapping Section

Sept 2016 - Till date

- Cad to GIS migration along with cartography of City and county Maps
- Website updates and improvement

Summer Internship at U Services – University of Minnesota

June 2016 - Aug 2016

• Developing a 3 dimensional (3D) campus map viewer using ArcGIS pro and JavaScript API. Creating PDF maps & Map books for several departments in the university. Creating a Web App for visualizing Nitrate simulation.

Graduate Assistant at U Services, University of Minnesota

Aug 2015 – June 2016

- Creating cartographically pleasing pdf and web maps from spatial data and AutoCAD files, spatial analysis, creating
 Python tools for process automation. Developing web applications like Campus maps, Snow tow Heat maps,
 Gender-neutral restroom data analysis, etc.
- GIS Data Curation, Managing ArcGIS Server and Data cataloging for the Enterprise geodatabase consisting of Terabytes of data.

Summer Internship at U Services - University of Minnesota

June 2015 - Aug 2015

- Deliverable were Interactive Map Development, Technical Documentation, and Reflection paper.
- Study & provide potential options for the development of the Interactive map.
- Understanding database management, project requirements and customizing using JavaScript API HTML & CSS. Working with ArcGIS online templates and following University codes and standards.

Cybertech India - ESRI Technical Support Redlands CA (GIS Analyst)

Jan 2012-Jul 2013

- Providing technical assistance to internal and external clients for customizing the existing product, understanding gaps and achieving required functionalities.
- Mentored and trained fresh hires. Worked mostly on ArcObjects for .Net SDK

Technical Competency:

- Languages: VB.NET, C#, ASP.Net, C++, VB 6.0, SQL, HTML, ASP, XML
- Database: PostgreSQL, MS Access, SQL, Oracle 9i
- Tools: Visual Studio 2012, Python scripter, Adobe illustrator cc, Dreamweaver, Eclipse, NetBeans 6.0

GIS software:

• ArcGIS Desktop (9.3, 10, 10.1, 10.3), ArcGIS Server Administration, PG-Admin, ERDAS Imagine, Terrasync, ArcPad 7.0, ArcGIS Pro, QGIS, ArcGIS online, Carto DB, ArcGIS Web AppBuilder, Trimble GPS device, GPS Garmin device

GIS developing platform:

- Python scripting, ArcObjects with C# & VB.net,
- Basic knowledge on JavaScript API, Google API, Leaflet, Bootstrap

Honors & Leadership Skills:

- Volunteering at Courage Kenney Rehabilitation Institute '15.
- Women's Affinity Group Leader for cultural events in Polytechnic level '07.
- Event leader for Robotics Workshop '11
- Lead actress of Firodiya Karandak (An intercollegiate Drama competition) '08.